webtoolsandtips.com 2013-03-24

# Internet Security Blog | Privacy Policy

Updated as on July 1st, 2008.

[Webtools & Tips](http://webtoolsandtips.com/) is a personal blog, owned by [Silki Garg](http://webtoolsandtips.com/about/).

[Webtools & Tips](http://webtoolsandtips.com/) strongly believes in the importance of keeping readers’ personal information personal. It will never use your information for any use beyond that stated or the permissions you give us. And that is the precise reason, we think appropriate to write this page.

**Visitor Tracking**

[Webtools & Tips](http://webtoolsandtips.com/) uses Analytical Tools like Google Analytics, and for this purpose a few stats like IP, browser, screen resolution, operating system are captured. This information is used solely for monitoring the volume of traffic the site receives and measuring the number of readers. We do not use the information for tracking the activities of specific visitors to the site or share it with any other third party for any reason.

**Cookies**

[Webtools & Tips](http://webtoolsandtips.com/) uses cookies just to remember you like most of the sites on Internet today. The purpose is to customize the site as per your preferences. They do not contain any personal information. Sometimes, cookies are also used by third party advertisers, who give their ads on [Webtools & Tips](http://webtoolsandtips.com/).

**Advertising**

[Webtools & Tips](http://webtoolsandtips.com/) runs advertising for meeting its maintenance costs. These adverts are served from our advertising servers as well as from third-party ad servers managed by the advertiser. We are not responsible to the Privacy Policy of these advertisers. Users of [Webtools & Tips](http://webtoolsandtips.com/) are advised to check the policies of these advertisers themselves.

These ad servers may attempt to set cookies on your computer. All these sites stress that information gathered through these cookies is used purely for the purpose of advert delivery, recording and segmentation. They do not use information gathered through their cookies for their own use, and they do not collect any personally identifiable information.

We also use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**E-mail**

Many of the users of [Webtools & Tips](http://webtoolsandtips.com/) prefer to get the latest post delivered to them through Email. We run this service through FeedBurner. If you supply us with your e-mail address, you may receive periodic e-mails from us. We do not share it with third parties, never.

**Questions and Comments**

You may direct questions, comments or reports on our [contact us](http://webtoolsandtips.com/contact-us/) page.

**Revisions to the Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is dynamic. It will continually change. Unless, in the sole opinion of the website, this policy changes so drastically as to suggest a posted notification on the site or via email, you will receive no notification of changes to this Privacy Policy nor, under any circumstances, does this site promise notification. Your continued use of this site always evidences your acceptance of the terms this Privacy Policy or any modifications.

**Final Words**

That said, be assured that we also want Internet to be a better place. We will never harm your Privacy or your interest.

**(Silki Garg)**
